https://biggideas.com/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
We collect and use personal information you have provided to us solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us or you and for other compatible purposes. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. We also collect ip address, time date stamp of inquiry, and browser used for the purpose of improving the security of our web site, and for no other purpose.
We never share any information you provide or your email to third parties for any reason. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Need A Quote?
© Copyright 1996-2019 Big Ideas™ Parade Giants™. All Rights Reserved BIPG™
Giant Inflatables and Advertising Balloons for Parades and Special Events.
